好，你好吗？
Good good how are you?
buenas buenas buenas cómo andan?
一切好吗？
all good?
todo bien?
我在这里和桑蒂在一起，我在寻找一些音乐
I'm with Santi here, I was looking for some music
estoy con Santi acá, estaba buscando un poco de música
我发现自己在这里，我会看到什么？
I have found myself here, what am I going to see?
Me he encontrado aquí, ¿qué voy a poner a ver?
我刚到三个小时前的背景中有一点我到达了这个排位赛的日期
There is a little in the background I am just arrived about three hours ago I arrived that incredible this qualifying date
hay un poquito de fondo estoy recién llegado hace unas tres cuatro horas llegué que increíble esta fecha eliminatoria
我认为我们想发生的一切都很理想。
I think everything we wanted to happen came out ideal.
creo que salió ideal todo lo que queríamos que pase pasó.
我的头目标失踪了
My head goal was missing
Faltó mi gol de cabeza
我保持很高，也就是说，跳回去，我不能给他十字架，我不能
I stay very high, that is, jumping back and I can't give him the cross and I couldn't
me quedo muy alta o sea que saltando para atrás y no le puedo dar la quise cruzar y no pude
请聊天这个FIFA日期是什么。
We are going to chat a little of what this FIFA date was, please.
Vamos a charlar un poco de lo que fue esta fecha FIFA, por favor.
对我来说，这是理想的日期。
For me it was the ideal date.
Para mí fue la fecha ideal.
而且它不能更加完美，像这样的6分，以及实现2场比赛的方式。
And it cannot be more perfect, 6 points like that and in the way that the 2 games were achieved.
Y no se puede ser más perfecta, 6 puntos así y de la manera que se consiguieron los 2 partidos.
对我来说，这是理想的。
For me it was ideal.
Para mí fue ideal.
完美的事情就是这样。
Perfect that would have been so.
Perfecto que hubiese sido así.
对我来说，这是一个目标。
For me it has been a goal.
Para mí individualmente ha sido un gol.
愿乌拉圭赢得胜利。
May Uruguay win as if he won.
Que gano el de Uruguay como si le gano estuvo bien.
正是在乌拉圭，我们非常……我们必须做我们必须做的事情，我们很公平并且赢得了胜利。
It was that with Uruguay we were very ... we had to do what we had to do, there we were fair and won.
Es que con Uruguay fuimos muy... Teníamos que hacer lo que teníamos que hacer, ahí fuimos justos y ganamos.
您是如何看待Asimene的？
How did you do to see Asimene?
¿Cómo hiciste para ver a Asimene?
不，我没看到他。
No, I didn't see him.
No, no lo vi.
今天，当我看到罗德里（Rodri）时，我正在和桑蒂（Santi）交谈...
Today I was talking to Santi when I see Rodri ...
hoy justo estaba hablando con Santi cuando veo que Rodri...
我在那里有球，没有人在空间上标记我是阳光，在第一个控制中
I had the ball there and nobody was marking I piqua to space I was very sun and in the first control
tenía la pelota ahí y nadie estaba marcando le piqué al espacio quedé solísimo y en el primer control
好吧，现在让我们看看剧本，我将利用这两个游戏，让我们看看这两个游戏。
Well now let's see the play, I'm going to take advantage and let's see both games.
Bueno ahora vamos a ver la jugada, voy a aprovechar y vamos a ver los dos partidos.
在控制的控制中，我认为我有一个空间可以在防守者和弓箭手之间放置
In the control that I do I think I have a space to put it between defender and archer but it is like that
en el control que hago creo que tengo un espacio para meterla entre defensor y arquero pero es como que
我看到了一点
I saw it a bit just then I waited a second more to put it behind the sensor
lo vi un poco justo entonces esperé un segundo más para meterla por detrás del sensor
以为亚历克西斯在防守者周围跑来跑去
Thinking that Alexis was running around the defender was going to stop to wait for her back
Pensando que por ahí Alexis cuando corría a la par del defensor se iba a frenar como para esperarla atrás
它跟着我，我说我来朱利亚诺（Giuliano
And it followed me, and I said that I came to Giuliano for the second stick, but no, beautiful, beautiful, not only for the goal that, but for ...
y me siguió, y decí que venía a Giuliano por el segundo palo, pero no, hermoso, hermoso todo, no solo por el gol ese, sino por...
尽管我们在第一分钟打了一个完整的体育场，尽管邮政 - 驻座票出现了多么昂贵
As we played the first minute a full stadium, despite how expensive the post -stadium tickets came out
por como jugamos el primer minuto una locura estadio repleto a pesar de lo caro que salían las entradas estadio repleto
您必须说，您也必须感谢人们，这总是伴随的。
You have to say it, you have to thank people too, which always accompanies.
Hay que decirlo, hay que agradecerle a la gente también, que siempre acompaña.
那太棒了。
That's great.
Eso es genial.
看起来他们已经开始准备，已经很清楚他们想如何玩，他们想玩4、4、2
Look they have already started preparing, there is already clear how they wanted to play, they wanted to play 4, 4, 2
miren ellos ya se empezaron a preparar, ahi ya se ve claro como querian jugar ellos, querian jugar 4, 4, 2
要打4-4-2，这实际上是可能的。
To play the 4-4-2, this is practically possible.
Para jugar los 4-4-2 así es prácticamente posible.
首先是因为我们有3个中场。
First because we have 3 midfielders.
Primero porque tenemos 3 medio encampistas.
我将尝试说最战术的三个半露营者，对其中两个已经少了一个
I'm going to try to speak the most tactical three half campists against two of them already have one less
yo voy a tratar de hablar lo más táctico tres medio campistas contra dos de ellos ahí ya tienen uno menos
加上您与守门员相处的事实，他们在这件事中不及格，并加上我在这里看不到的事实
added to the fact that you have both in Trail with the goalkeeper who make the 3 against this and added to the fact that I do not see in this play here
sumado a que tenés los dos en trail con el arquero que le hacen el 3 contra 2 a este y sumado a que te hago que no se ve en esta jugada acá
媒介去那里，我们已经赢了，动作即将到来，一个来了，我们有很多
The medium goes down there, we were already winning this, the movements is coming, one comes, we have very much
baja mucho el medio ahí ya le estábamos ganando esto es algo clave los movimientos uno va otro viene ya tenemos muy
直到下一次。
until next time.
hasta la próxima.
看，想和两个罢工者一起按5的阵阵阵阵，守门员4对2
Look, want to come to press with the two strikers having the two centrals at 5 free and goalkeeper 4 against 2
Mira, quiere venir a presionar con los dos delanteros teniendo a los dos centrales al 5 libre y al arquero 4 contra 2
看，四个数。
Look, four counted.
Mira, cuatro contados.
你好吗？
How do you do?
¿Cómo hace?
回到这一边。
Back, for this side.
De vuelta, para este lado.
我该怎么办？
What do I do?
¿Qué hago yo?
我把它拖给我，我接受。
I drag it to me, I take it.
Me lo arrastro, me lo llevo.
你想和4一起玩吗？
Do you want to play with 4?
¿Quieren jugar con 4?
他们手头，他们想继续。
Hand in hand, they want to continue.
Mano a mano, quieren seguir.
好吧，还有另一个空间。
Well, space for another.
Bueno, espacio para otra.
发生了什么事？
What's happening?
¿Qué pasa?
Tiago，极端，低。
Tiago, extreme, low.
Tiago, extremo, baja.
谁跟随？
Who follows?
Quién lo sigue?
没有人。
Nobody.
Nadie.
准备好，一个人收到。
Ready, receive alone.
Listo, recibe sola.
因为另一面是最终与巴西对抗的关键
As the other side was key in the end you play against a Brazil that
como para otro lado era clave al final vos juegas contra un Brasil que
以前不是巴西，而是喜欢球。
It is not the Brazil before, but who likes to have the ball.
No es el Brasil de antes, pero que le gusta tener la pelota.
巴西总是喜欢拥有球，做...
Brazil always likes to have the ball, do ...
A Brasil siempre le gusta tener la pelota, hacer...
让竞争对手的奔跑不喜欢让球有许多巴西前锋和
Make the rival run not like to have the ball to run back had many Brazil strikers and
hacer correr al rival no les gusta no tener la pelota tener correr atrás tenía muchos delanteros brasil y
在球后跑步会杀死他们。
And running behind the ball kills them.
y correr atrás de la pelota los mata.
在扮演更多垂直触摸器之前，它不是巴西，而更多的极端触摸。
It is not Brazil before there played many more vertical touchers, more extremes that are hand in hand.
No es el Brasil de antes que por ahí jugaba a muchos toqueores más verticales, más extremos que van mano a mano.
在这里，它所读的是构建三个三个线，相同两个
And here what it does read is to build a line of three three against two the same
y acá lo que hace lea es armar una línea de tres tres contra dos lo mismo
3矛盾2。
3 contra 2.
到处都有空间。
There is space everywhere.
Empieza a haber espacio en todos lados.
这是第一个进球，我跑一侧，看4只后卫，中央不能离开，这想为我得分
This is the first goal play, I run the side, look 4 defenders, the central cannot leave, this wants to score me
Esta es la jugada de primer gol, le corro a la lateral, miren 4 defensores, el central no puede salir, este me quiere marcar a mi
圣地亚哥（Santiago
Santiago receives, turns very well without touching the ball and Juli has that ...
Santiago recibe, gira muy bien sin tocar la pelota y Juli tiene esa...
与克罗地亚一样，寻找他们全部的前命运都有篮板，这都是令人难以置信的。
That front fate that looks for them all, as the same with Croatia, has the rebounds, all incredible.
Esa suerte delantero que las busca toda, como igual con Croatia, le quedan los rebotes, todo increíble.
还有多少？
And how many?
¿Y van cuántos?
3分钟。
3 minutes.
3 minutos.
这使我们更加安心。
This gave us even more peace of mind.
Esto nos dio más tranquilidad todavía.
在第4分钟以4-1-0获胜。
Go winning 4-1-0 in minute 4.
Ir ganando 4-1-0 en el minuto 4.
它转身，并不是那么精心阐述，看，转弯，在中间接收，我跑了罗德里，见到我
It turns and was not so elaborate, look, turns, receives in the middle, I run Rodri, sees me
Se gira y no fue tan elaborada, mira, se gira, recibe en el medio, le corro a Rodri, me ve
他被降低到蒂亚戈（Tiago）的蒂亚戈（Tiago），而没有触摸完美的巡回演出
He is lowered to Tiago, Tiago without touching the perfect tour
Se la bajo a Tiago, Tiago sin tocar la gira Perfecto
它不是那么精致，而是有力的。
It was not so elaborate, but forceful.
No fue tan elaborada, pero contundente.
再次。
Again.
Otra vez.
中间比赛总是免费的球员，莱安德罗总是
Middle play always free players, Leandro always
juego de juego de medio siempre jugadores libres, Leandro Solo siempre
恩佐（Enzo）在这边只有我不再跟随我再跟着拉菲哈（Rafinha）减去三个前锋罗德里戈（Rodrigo）4
Enzo on this side only me no longer follows me any more rafinha minus three strikers Rodrigo 4
enzo de este lado solo a mí ya no me sigue más rafinha menos tres delanteros rodrigo 4
4 2 4切口
4 2 4 Cut
4 2 4 cortados
这里发生了什么？
What happens here?
¿Qué es lo que pasa acá?
恩佐（Enzo
Enzo begins to drive, begins to bring on side 4-2
Enzo empieza a conducir, empieza a traer al lateral 4-2
您开始寻找侧面，您不能离开它，因为我是乐队，如果我得到的，请给我
You start looking for the side, you can't leave it because I'm by band, if I get it, give me
empiezas a buscar al lateral, no lo puedes salir porque estoy yo por banda, si me sale me la dame
它吸引，去吸引，吸引，吸引...当然，他不知道该怎么办，是外出还是等我。
It attracts, goes, attracts, attracts, attracts ... of course, he doesn't know what to do, whether to go out or wait for me.
Atrae, va, atrae, atrae, atrae... Claro, este no sabe qué hacer, si salirle o esperarme a mí.
几乎三个四个四个普坦想到三个假设他们，但是罗德里很孤单
Look three almost for three four Putan Suppose them but well Rodri is alone
miren tres casi para tres tres cuatro pongan suponganles pero bueno Rodri está solo
今天一个人都在内部关闭，戏剧在外面
Today alone, all closed inside, the play outside
hoy solo, todos cerrados adentro, la jugada afuera
你好。
Hello.
Hola.
它触摸它，但没有到达。
There it touches it, but it doesn't arrive.
Ahí la toca, pero no llega.
30和Touch Peak是这，对吗？
30 and touch peak was this, right?
30 y pico de toque fue esta ¿no?
不，不，我们移动的方式是...
No, no, the way we moved it was ...
No, no, la manera en que la movimos fue...
一切顺利
Everything goes well but because the game is also guided to you what you have to do where the spaces are 33 touches
sale todo bien pero porque también el juego te va guiando lo que hay que hacer donde están los espacios 33 toques
空间在哪里？
Where are the spaces?
¿Dónde están los espacios?
玩的地方在哪里？
Where are the places to play?
¿Dónde están los lugares para jugar?
来4-2-4，他们已经开始削减了
Come 4-2-4, they are already starting to cut
Ven 4-2-4, ya se están empezando a cortar
因此，在前15个之前，他已经赢得了2到0的胜利是Cuti Play
Thus, before the first 15 he is already winning 2 to 0 here is the Cuti play
así ante los primeros 15 ya está ganando 2 a 0 acá está la jugada del cuti
他相信这一点
He trusts thinking that this
se confía pensando que éste
我再也没有见到她。
I didn't see her again.
No la volví a ver.
当他将搭便车重新放回里面时，他想找到除可爱以外的其他通行证。
When he makes the hitch back inside, he wants to find another pass other than the cutie.
Cuando hace el enganche de vuelta para adentro, para mí quiere buscar otro pase que no sea el cutie.
你吃了他，你看到了吗？
And you ate him, do you see?
y le comió, ves?
当它放慢时
Here when it slows
acá cuando frena
我不想给我...我不知道。
I didn't want to give it to me ... I don't know.
Para mí se la... No se la quiso dar a... No sé.
我不知道他是想把它交给OTA还是回去绘画。
I don't know if he wanted to give it to Ota or go back to give it to Draw.
No sé si quiso dársela a Ota o volver atrás para dársela a Dibu.
在这种触摸中，他赢得了它，他们对此有什么质量
And in that touch he won it and what they have to this is that he has a lot of quality
y en ese toque de más se la ganó y lo que tienen a esto es que tiene mucha calidad
控制，弧线和目标。
Control, arc and goal.
Control, al arco y gol.
迪格跑了很困难。
And the Digú was running back, very difficult.
Y el Digú estaba corriendo hacia atrás, muy difícil.
但是好吧，我什至告诉你，如果不是那场比赛，我们仍然做出了更多的目标。
But well, I even tell you if it hadn't been for this play, we still made more goals.
Pero bueno, incluso te digo si no hubiese sido por esta jugada, por ahí le hacíamos más goles todavía.
再次，两个反对一个。
Again, two against one.
Otra vez, dos contra uno.
哦，我以为有人要到达，Boludo，第二把棍子，他们是第一个。
Oh, I thought someone was going to arrive, boludo, the second stick, they were the whole first.
Ay, yo pensé que iba a llegar alguien, boludo, el segundo palo, fueron todo el primero.
我记得比
I remember more than
más me acuerdo que
我记得我要把中心扔在下面，但是当它被扔到地板上时，我说喙是第三
I remember that I was going to throw the center below but when it was thrown to the floor I say the beak here comes the third
me acuerdo que iba a tirar el centro por abajo pero cuando se tiró al piso digo la pico acá viene el tercero
恩佐（Enzo）和啤酒（Ale
Beautiful pass from Enzo and Ale VERY WELL RUNING IN THE SECOND LINE, BEAUTIFUL PASS
hermoso pase de Enzo y Ale muy bien corriendo en la segunda línea, hermoso pase
我问他，他告诉我，守门员看到了他，然后出去，然后他要碰她，他以为他们会打破一切，但没有。
I asked him and he told me that the goalkeeper saw him, going out then he was going to touch her, he thought they were going to break everything, but no.
Le pregunté y me dijo que lo vio el arquero, salir entonces la iba a tocar de una, pensó que le iban a romper todo, pero no.
他告诉我，如果我看到他离开，但我以为他会打破一切而没有到达。
He told me if I saw him leave but I thought he was going to break everything and did not arrive.
Me dijo si lo vi salir pero pensé que me iba a romper todo y no llegó.
没有什么可触摸它的。
There was nothing to touch it.
Estuvo nada de tocarlo.
而且，我认为轮到您了。
Moreover, I think it's your turn.
Es más, creo que lo toca.
美丽的通行证。
Beautiful pass.
Hermoso pase.
而且也有很多定义，第一个这样的定义...
And there is a lot of definition too, the first like this ...
y hay mucha definición también, el primero así...
但这是我们的全部，我认为他在巴西也离开了两次
But it's all our boludo, I think he left for twice as well in Brazil
pero es todo nuestro boludo creo que partió dos veces nada más en Brasil
我像过去一样呆着，我想越过它，但我没有给出方向。
I stayed like the past and I wanted to cross it and I didn't give it direction.
Quedé como pasado y la quise cruzar y no le di dirección.
âgracias！
¡Gracias!
VES？
¿Ves?
就像我跳回去，我想越过它。
It's like I jumped back and I wanted to cross it.
Es como que salté para atrás y la quise cruzar.
看，甚至在第一个棍子上，Boludo。
Look, there even to the first stick, boludo.
Mira vos, por ahí incluso hasta el primer palo, boludo.
这...不，Boludo，我...是的，交叉的，这就是为什么。
And this ... no, boludo, I'm ... yes, crossed hand, that's why.
Y esta... No, boludo, estoy... Sí, mano cruzada, por eso.
不，这里发生的是我的第一遍
No, here what happens is this in the first pass that is where I
no, acá lo que pasa es esto en primer pase ahí es donde donde yo
你看到我有点长时间，我做了一步
You see that I have a bit long to the coso and I do one step
ves que me queda un poco larga hasta el coso y hago un paso más
在那里，我爱她，我把她提前前进，但我不知道这是如何快速的。
There I loved her, I put her ahead, but I didn't know how it was in speed.
Ahí yo la quise, la meto por delante, pero no sabía cómo venía esta en velocidad.
如果我要切下它，我就把它放回那里
If I was going to cut it or not then I put it back there
si me lo iba a cortar o no entonces yo la meto por atrás ahí
我说，有停下来，朱利安（Julian）到达后面。
And I say, there is stops, and well, Julian arrived behind.
y digo, por ahí se frena, y bueno, llegó Juliano por atrás.
我没有看到她前方，...
I didn't see her ahead, and ...
No la vi por delante, y...
这里是在后面完成的，没有出错。
Here it is done behind and did not go wrong.
Aquí se hace por atrás y no salió mal.
莱加诺离开我，罗德里见到我。
Legano leaves me, Rodri sees me.
Me deja legano, Rodri me ve.
在那个控制中，它在前方，我没有看到它，说，它停止了。
In that control it was ahead and I did not see it and say, it stops.
En ese control era por delante y no la vi y digo, se frena.
但是，如果现在在这里看到它，我告诉你我本可以踢它，碰巧一个人一个人进入亚历克西斯，我不是自私的。
But if now seeing it here I tell you that I could have kicked it, it happens that entering Alexis very alone, I am not selfish.
pero si ahora viéndolo acá te digo que podría haber pateado pasa que entrando a Alexis muy solo así yo no soy egoísta me sale patear
4比1，令人难以置信的比赛，我认为还有更多比赛，这是任意球，希望您穿透Sanio
4 to 1, incredible game, I think there is some more play, this free kick, I hope you penetrate Sanio
4 a 1, increíble partido, creo que hay alguna jugada más, esta tiro libre, espero que penetre a Sanio
这场战斗已经很漂亮了
This fight is beautiful is the bank already
esta pelea es hermosa la viene el banco ya
可能是第五或第六
It could have been a fifth or sixth
podría haber sido un quinto o un sexto
不。
No.
如果我在这里跑步，那是5-1对吗？
And if I had been running here, it was for a 5-1 right?
Y si me venía corriendo para acá, era para un 5-1 ¿no?
不，甚至目标已经是我们的。
No, even the goal was already ours.
No, incluso el gol fue ya nuestro.
是的，嗯，IBU的游乐场。
Yes, well, the IBU's playgrounds.
Sí, bueno, los jueguitos del Ibu.
您如何看待IBIB的游戏？
What do you think of the IBIB's games?
¿Qué piensas de los jueguitos del Ibu?
我认为很好。
I think it was fine.
Yo creo que estuvo bien.
它不会滥用。
It does not abuse.
No se abuso.
他给了他传球，当他控制它时，他很高，那么他可能已经做了很小的比赛并降低了比赛，并又做了两个球员
He gives him the pass back and when he controls it, he is high then he may have made that little game and lower it and made two more players
él le dan el pase atrás le queda picando y cuando la controla le queda alta entonces por ahí puede haber hecho ese jueguito y bajarla e hizo dos jueguitos más
这并不疯了。
It was not crazy.
No fue una locura.
他没有虐待。
He did not abuse.
No abusó.
不，这就是为什么。
No, that's why.
No, por eso.
好吧。
Alright.
Está bien.
我已经在银行里看着他，说，不，不，帕里，停下来，不要成为boludo。
I was already in the bank and looked at him and says, no, no, paraly, stop, don't be a boludo.
Yo ya estaba en el banco y lo miraba y le dice, no, no, pará, pará, no seas boludo.
他不喜欢那些东西。
He doesn't like those things.
No le gustan esas cosas.
例如，拉芬哈（Rafinha），您如何看待Rafinha？
Rafinha for example, what did you think of Rafinha?
Lo de Rafinha por ejemplo, ¿para vos qué pensabas de Rafinha?
对我来说，他们知道发生了什么事
For me they know what happened if
para mí saben lo que pasó si te
我们将有点分析面试，我觉得最终就像罗马里奥在要求
We are going to analyze the interview a bit, I feel that in the end it is like Romario is demanding
vamos a analizar un poco la entrevista, yo siento que al final es como que Romario le está exigiendo
对他说的一切是的。
to him say everything that yes.
a que él diga todo que sí.
对我来说，这也就像激励它。
For me it is also like motivating it.
Para mí también es como motivarlo.
好吧，当然。
Well, of course.
Bueno, claro, claro.
另一个人说是的，可以分析一个。
The other says yes, as saying, one can be analyzed.
El otro dice que sí, como diciendo, uno se puede analizar.
罗马里奥（Romario）要做，我不告诉你战斗，但这是巴西最好的球员之一。
Romario is up to, I do not tell you fighting, but it is one of the best players in Brazil.
Romario está a la altura de, no te digo de pelea, pero es uno de los mejores jugadores de Brasil.
所以这就像一个人成长，告诉你我们会赢，你告诉他
So it's like someone growing gross and tells you we will win and you tell him
entonces es como que venga alguien grosso grosso y te diga vamos a ganar y vos le digas
阿根廷人不好是我们会继续不继续的戴尔很瘦
Not good Argentine is okay is how Dale Skinny we will continue not
no bueno argentino está bien nosotros es como dale flaco vamos a continuar no no
因为你也会激励你
In that you get to motivate you too
en eso te agarras para motivarte vos también
我们是寻找激励措施的第一号。
We are the number one to look for an incentive.
Nosotros somos los número uno para buscar un incentivo.
因为我也认为这也有点
because I also think it was a bit too
porque además creo que fue un poco también es más creo que lo dice él
就像他们花了一点背景一样，您看到他们这样说，因为您看到报纸或笔记说
Like they took a little context, you saw that they put it that way because you see the newspapers or the notes say
como que le sacaron un poco de contexto viste como que se lo pusieron así porque vos ves los diarios o las notas dicen
我们将在场外和外面杀死它们
We are going to kill them inside and outside the field I am going to make a goal and it is not like he does not really say it
los vamos a matar adentro y afuera del campo les voy a hacer un gol y no es como que él no lo dice en realidad
他肯定了罗马里奥所说的他很清楚的
He affirms what Romario says he gets clear
Él afirma lo que dice Romario Él se sube Claro
但是非常不错的游戏非常好的游戏理想的FIFA约会6点已经分类到世界杯，这是对方所说的其他事情
But well very nice very nice game ideal FIFA date 6 points already classified to the World Cup that is other things that the other said
pero bueno muy lindo partido muy lindo fecha fifa ideal 6 puntos ya clasificados al mundial que es otras cosas que lo dije la otra
在注释中。
In a note.
en una nota.
我们不采用维度。
We do not take dimension.
No tomamos dimensión.
分类甚至没有庆祝。
The classification was not even celebrated.
Incluso no se festejó la clasificación.
世界杯就像我们不是欣快的我们被分类的
The World Cup is like we are not euphoric we are classified
al mundial es como que no no estamos eufóricos vamos clasificamos
也许是因为一个人已经有了它。
Maybe because one in the head already has it.
Quizás porque uno en la cabeza ya lo tiene.
即使有25分，您已经被分类为世界杯。
Even with 25 points you are already classified in World Cups.
Incluso con 25 puntos ya estás clasificado en mundiales prácticamente.
更多的是10个半的7个，因为您不给它很多
more being almost 6 and a half 7 of 10 as you don't give it a lot
más siendo casi 6 y medio 7 de 10 como que no le das mucha
这是一个狗屎，因为以后，您还记得巴勒莫的目标吗？
It's a shit, because later, do you remember Palermo's goal?
Es una cagada, porque después, ¿te acuerdas del gol de Palermo?
巴勒莫的进球，Closer，2018年，是对厄瓜多尔的最后一场比赛。
Palermo's goal, closer, 2018, the last game against Ecuador.
El gol de Palermo, más cerca, 2018, el último partido contra Ecuador.
确切的是我们赢得了厄瓜多尔，那就好像我们不在维度上
Exact that we won Ecuador then it is like that we do not take it in dimension
exacto que le ganamos ecuador entonces es como que eso no lo tomamos en dimensión
它的含义。
of what it means.
de lo que significa.
也许是因为我们做得很好，以至于……是的，这样做是正常的，您看到了吗？
Maybe because we are doing so well that it is like ... and yes, it is normal to do it, did you see?
Quizás porque lo estamos haciendo tan bien que es como... Y sí, es normal hacerlo, ¿viste?
但是不，这不是正常的。
But no, it is not normal.
Pero no, no es normal.
因此，乐队正在聚集谈话，看看您是否可以乘坐飞机，我认为您可以去
So band are gathering talk to see if you can who can not take a plane I think you can go
así que banda vayan juntando platita a ver si se pueden el que no puede tomarse un avión creo que en auto se puede ir no
全部适合巴拿马，像这样的一切都可以跨越我认为您可以在全球到2026年之前穿越
All for Panama everything like this to cross the I think you can but go crossing by the year 2026 that comes worldwide
todo por panamá todo así para cruzar el yo creo que se puede pero vayan cruzando para el año 2026 que se viene mundial
他们骑自行车，摩托车...好吧，是的，他们已经骑自行车到达了卡塔尔，所以美国靠近了。
They go by bicycle, motorcycle ... well, yes, they have arrived by bike to Qatar, so the United States closer.
que van en bicicleta, moto... Bueno, sí, han llegado en bici hasta Qatar, así que Estados Unidos más cerca.
现在让我们看看表的样子，我们已经与31分类，图片分类
Now let's see how the table is, we are already classified with 31, the picture
Ahora vamos a ver como esta la tabla, nosotros ya estamos clasificados con 31, el cuadro
在第二个23乌拉圭21巴西21
By second 23 Uruguay 21 Brazil 21
por segundo 23 uruguay 21 brasil 21
哥伦比亚哥伦比亚哥伦比亚哥伦比亚20
Paraguay, Colombia 20, Mira Colombia had gone from being second to be sixth now
Paraguay, Colombia 20, mira Colombia había pasado de estar segundo a estar sexto ahora
好吧，这剩下四个日期，在这里我告诉你，它们都不是
Well, a matter that there are four dates left and here I tell you that they are not either
bueno cuestión de que quedan cuatro fechas y acá estos te digo que no están tampoco
这些不是保险，但同时它们具有很好的优势
These are not insured but at the same time they have very good advantage
Estos no están asegurados pero a la vez tienen muy buena ventaja
我想看看接下来的比赛与他们是谁。
I would like to see the next games against who they are.
Me gustaría ver los próximos partidos contra quienes son.
日期15。
Date 15.
Fecha 15.
厄瓜多尔巴西·琳达（Linda），很漂亮，因为如果厄瓜多尔赢了...
Ecuador Brazil Linda, pretty date because if Ecuador wins ...
Ecuador Brasil linda, linda fecha porque si Ecuador gana...
我把它留在巴西，我告诉你，即使我可以在委内瑞拉玻利维亚第六名
I leave it Brazil I tell you I can leave it even in sixth place Venezuela Bolivia
lo deja lo deja brasil te digo lo puedo dejar hasta en el sexto puesto venezuela bolivia
如果委内瑞拉在家中获胜的比赛将达到18分，那就需要四分
What game that if Venezuela winning from home goes to 18 it takes four points
que partido ese si Venezuela ganando de local se va a 18 le saca cuatro puntos
大约有九个危险的他有玻利维亚
About nine at stake he has all Bolivia
sobre nueve en juego tiene ganar todo Bolivia
委内瑞拉没有赢，但在我看来，这是委内瑞拉玻利维亚的决赛，我什至告诉你，如果委内瑞拉获胜并离开18
that Venezuela does not win but it seems to me that it is a final there Venezuela Bolivia and I even tell you that if Venezuela wins and leaves 18
que no gane venezuela pero me parece que es una final ahí venezuela bolivia y te digo incluso que si venezuela gana y se va 18
照顾哥伦比亚秘鲁，我在那里很难看到他们，因为他们在哥伦比亚比赛
Care Colombia Peru I see them difficult there because they play in Colombia
cuidado colombia perú a los peruanos los veo difíciles ahí porque encima juegan en colombia
非常艰难，因为如果他们失去了他们几乎在智利外面的智利在家中也对阵我们也是同一件事
Very hard because if they lose that they are almost outside Chile plays against us at home that also the same thing too
durísimo porque si llegan a perder ese ya están casi afuera Chile juega contra nosotros en su casa que también lo mismo
他必须赢得“是”或“是”对我们的胜利，因为他实际上也出去了。
He has to win yes or yes against us, because he is also out practically.
tiene que ganar sí o sí contra nosotros, pues sino también queda fuera prácticamente.
我们已经被分类了。
We are already classified.
Nosotros ya estamos clasificados.
毕竟，巴拉圭 - 鲁鲁格赛的比赛之后，一场精美的比赛也非常适合没有维克多的五场比赛，我也想更多
After all Paraguay-Uruguay match, a beautiful game also has been very good for five games without Victor and I think some more also
después de todo partido Paraguay-Uruguay lindo partido también Paraguay viene muy bien cinco partidos sin victor y creo que alguno más también
巴拉圭非常好，如果您击败乌拉圭，则可以将第二或第三名放置。
Paraguay is very good and if you beat Uruguay you can put the second or third.
muy bien viene Paraguay y si le gana a Uruguay se puede poner el segundo o tercero.
在我看来，这里最重要的政党将是委内瑞拉 - 巴利维亚。
It seems to me that the most important party here will be Venezuela-Bolivia.
Me parece que el partido más importante acá va a ser Venezuela-Bolivia.
开始。
Starting.
Partidazo.
很棒，因为他们在那里玩可以重新发作的人。
Great because they play there who can get into repechage.
Partidazo porque se juegan ahí el quién puede entrar en repechaje.
今天是委内瑞拉。
Today is Venezuela up.
Hoy está Venezuela arriba.
我告诉你，我不知道抽奖是否服务于委内瑞拉，因为我相信秘鲁和智利很难
And I tell you that I don't know if the draw serves Venezuela because I believe that Peru and Chile have it difficult
y te digo que no sé si el empate le sirve a Venezuela porque yo creo que Perú y Chile la tienen difícil
他们甚至有1点，但2和玻利维亚知道，在他们的法庭上，他们变得非常艰难。
They even with one point are up but 2 and Bolivia know that on their court they become very hard.
Ellos hasta con un punto siguen arriba pero a 2 y Bolivia sabemos que en su cancha se hacen muy muy duros.
日期16美国与哥伦比亚的玻利维亚智利卡萨
Date 16 us as with Colombia at Bolivia Chile Casa
fecha 16 nosotros como con colombia en casa bolivia chile
但是，如果我们击败智利，那已经是。
But if we beat Chile it is already.
Pero si le ganamos a Chile ya está.
这是什么意义？
Is this in what sense?
¿Ello está en qué sentido?
智利？
For Chile?
¿Para Chile?
如果他们在玻利维亚法院对抗玻利维亚
And if, then they play against Bolivia on Bolivia court, at the height
y si, después juegan contra Bolivia en cancha de Bolivia, en la altura
乌拉圭 - 委内瑞拉，这对委内瑞拉来说是另一个重要的游戏，但是乌拉圭和抽奖我认为我会成为代码。
Uruguay-Venezuela, well another important game for Venezuela, but Uruguay and a draw I think I would be code.
Uruguay-Venezuela, bueno otro partido importante para Venezuela, pero Uruguay ya un empate yo creo que estaría en clave.
几乎里面，秘鲁厄瓜多尔也将使秘鲁很难对我来说很难
Almost inside and Peru Ecuador will also have it difficult Peru has it very difficult for me
casi adentro y Perú Ecuador también la va a tener difícil Perú la tiene muy difícil para mí
日期17可以定义我们所有人在委内瑞拉，委内瑞拉在那里对我来说将在我的舞台上
And date 17 that this can define all of us play with Venezuela, Venezuela there for me will be in the stage of
y fecha 17 que esta puede definir todo nosotros jugamos con Venezuela, Venezuela ahí para mí va a estar en la etapa de
查看它们是分类还是因为玻利维亚与哥伦比亚在哥伦比亚杜罗·巴拉圭厄瓜多尔一起玩
to see whether they classify or because Bolivia plays with Colombia in Colombia Duro Paraguay Ecuador
de ver si clasifican o porque encima bolivia juega con colombia en colombia duro paraguay ecuador
可能是可以与巴西一起服务的两个智利比赛
It can be a result there that can serve the two Chile plays with Brazil
puede ser un resultado ahí que le pueda servir a los dos Chile juega con Brasil
智利在家里对阵我们，玻利维亚在室外和巴西与巴西一起
Chile plays against us at home, with Bolivia outside and with Brazil in Brazil
Chile juega contra nosotros en su casa, con Bolivia afuera y con Brasil en Brasil
好吧，在我的最后日期，一切都将被定义。
Well, on the last date for me, everything will be defined.
Bueno, ya en la última fecha para mí ya va a estar todo definido.
玻利维亚 - 巴西在玻利维亚。
Bolivia-Brazil in Bolivia.
Bolivia-Brasil en Bolivia.
厄瓜多尔 - 阿根廷，因为我的厄瓜多尔A几乎也应该被分类。
Ecuador-Argentina, for my Ecuador A should almost have been classified as well.
Ecuador-Argentina, para mi Ecuador a casi debería haber estado clasificado también.
委内瑞拉 - 哥伦比亚？
Venezuela-Colombia?
¿Venezuela-Colombia?
是的，委内瑞拉将在很大程度上取决于每场比赛的发生。
Yes, Venezuela will depend a lot on what every game happens.
Sí, Venezuela va a depender mucho de qué pase cada partido.
智利和乌拉圭。
Chile and Uruguay.
Chile y Uruguay.
也就是说，他对乌拉圭也去了辣椒。
That is, against Uruguay he also went to the chiles.
O sea, contra Uruguay también fue a los chiles.
也就是说，智利是不可能的。
That is, impossible for Chile.
O sea, imposible para Chile.
但是，任何事情都可能发生。
But well, anything can happen.
Pero bueno, puede pasar cualquier cosa.
如果我获胜，2016年的穆尼兹将成为一个转折点。
The 2016 Muniz is going to be a turning point, if I win.
El Muniz 2016 va a ser un punto de inflexión, si gano se pierda.
是的，这是最后一支舞。
Yes, it's the last dance.
Si, es el last dance.
好吧，来了，他们说最后一支舞。
Well, there come, they say Last dance.
Bueno, ahí ven, dicen Last Dance.
在2022年，但这是最后一支舞。
In 2022, but it was Last Dance.
En 2022, pero ha sido Last Dance.
但是，由于它发生了，所以它最终并没有是最后一支舞。
However, because it occurred, it did not end up being Last Dance.
Sin embargo, por cómo se dio, no terminó siendo el Last Dance.
因为我们自2021年以来就离开了冠军。
Because we had left champion since 2021 of the Copa América.
Porque nosotros habíamos salido campeón desde el 2021 de la Copa América.
我们说，就是这样。
We said, that's it.
Dijimos, ya está.
好吧，我们没有说，但是一个人已经是选择的冠军，真是令人难以置信。
Well, we didn't say, but one is already champion in the selection and it is Wow, incredible.
Bueno, no dijimos, pero uno ya sale campeón en la selección y es wow, increíble.
您去了世界杯，那里他们没有赢得世界杯和BuenoBorrón和新帐户，您是从零回来开始的
You went to the World Cup and there they did not win the World Cup and Bueno Borrón and new account you start from Zero back
ibas al mundial y por ahí no se ganaban el mundial y bueno borrón y cuenta nueva empezás de cero de vuelta
因为对我来说狮子座，他没有赢
because for me leo out there and he didn't win
porque para mi Leo por ahí se iba y no se ganaba
当然，因为不知道会发生什么，但是今天...
Of course, because it is not known what could have happened, but today ...
Claro, sí, porque no se sabe lo que podría haber pasado, pero hoy en día...
2026可以是最后一支舞吗？
Can 2026 be a last dance?
¿El 2026 puede ser un last dance?
是的，怎么不呢？
Yes, how not?
Sí, ¿cómo no?
我的目标是到达2026年，然后我将看到自己的工作。
My goal is to get to 2026 and then I will see what I do.
Mi objetivo es llegar al 2026 y después veré qué hago.
那么，您将依赖我当时感觉的一切好的乐队，感谢您的支持，感谢您的支持
Then you will depend everything that I feel at that time good band I leave thanks for the support thanks for
después va a depender todo lo que de lo que sienta en ese momento bueno banda me voy gracias gracias por el apoyo gracias por
昨天今天，我们将找到我们可以随身携带的一切
For today yesterday we will find everything we can go with some subject
por el día de hoy el día de ayer vamos a darle con todo nos podemos ir con algún tema
Chau Chau Chau
chau chau chau
来制作框架
Come make frame
Vem fazer armação